<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Careers on BnB Systems</title><link>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/</link><description>Recent content in Careers on BnB Systems</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>copyright &amp;copy; 2020 all right reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://bnbsystems.org/careers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sales Representative</title><link>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/salesrepresentative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/salesrepresentative/</guid><description>Minimum qualifications at least 3 years of professional experience in sales or business development English is a must native speaker in German proactive approach and goal oriented experience with making cold calling extroverted personality, who actively seeks conversation and enjoys dealing with people Responsibilities implement an effective sales strategy that maximizes the value delivered by Bnb to our Clients (managing the entire sales cycle from finding a client to securing a deal) develop and widen a contact network that allows BnB services to be sold broadly and effectively provide professional after-sales support maintenance quality of data in CRM About the job As BnB grows we are expanding our Business Development Team and are looking for a new Teammate to join us.</description></item><item><title>React Developer</title><link>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/reactdeveloper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/reactdeveloper/</guid><description>Minimum qualifications at least a year of professional experience as react developer fluency in graphics programs (eg.</description></item><item><title>DevOps Engineer</title><link>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/devopsengineer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/devopsengineer/</guid><description>Minimum qualifications at least a year of professional experience in building software proven experience as a DevOps on Azure cloud provider (WebApps, Storage accounts, AD B2C, CosmosDB, Container registries) hands-on experience with Docker and terraform ability to solve network and application issues Responsibilities creating and constant improving of a delivery pipelines for various programming environments sharing knowledge with your colleagues building pipelines in GitHub About the job As BnB grows we are expanding our Business Development Team and are looking for a new Teammate to join us.</description></item><item><title>Account Executive</title><link>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/accountexecutive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/accountexecutive/</guid><description>Minimum qualifications proven experience as an Account Executive a successful track record in software sales for at least 2 years of professional experience working in software projects advanced English is a must Responsibilities create and implement an effective sales strategy that maximizes the value delivered by Bnb to our Clients (managing the entire sales cycle from finding a client to securing a deal) create detailed business plans designed to attain predetermined goals develop and widen a contact network that allows BnB services to be sold broadly and effectively provide professional after-sales support About the job As BnB grows we are expanding our Business Development Team and are looking for a new Teammate to join us.</description></item><item><title>C# Developer</title><link>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/csharpdeveloper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/csharpdeveloper/</guid><description>Minimum qualifications at least a year of professional experience as C# Developer on ASP.NET core fluency in .</description></item><item><title>R Developer</title><link>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/rdeveloper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbsystems.org/careers/positions/rdeveloper/</guid><description>Minimum qualifications at least a year of professional experience as R Developer fluency in R programming language and packages like plumber, knitr, dplyr, remotes mind of the researcher interest in capital markets or real estate Responsibilities building valuation model automation of financial reports in Rmarkdown building shiny apps for dashboards About the job As BnB grows we are expanding our Business Development Team and are looking for a new Teammate to join us.</description></item></channel></rss>